I was half dead.
I failed yet again to make Lady
Doux a cruel and vicious demon.
What exactly am I supposed to do?
No, no.
I guess I'm stuck.
Maybe I'll talk to Yairya about it.
What?!
Hey, all of you!
What's wrong? What in the world happened?
You can't be serious.
YAIRYA – FIRST-CLASS WITCH
Yairya!
At this rate, we witches are finished...
And Jahi...
it's all your fault.
What?!
THE WITCHES' POTIONS WORK WAY TOO GOOD!!
"The Witches' Potions
Work Way Too Good!!"
The witches are finished because of us?
What do you mean by that?
Take a look at this.
This is me...
Back then, His Majesty sent us to
invade various locations in
order to unify the demon world.
That's just it.
Huh?
Because you all expanded our territory,
DEMONS
more and more demons
who were in the castle
were sent out to various locations
for development and maintenance...
As a result, we ended up having
to do the work around the castle
that the demons were supposed to do!
We're supposed to concoct various potions,
but we're all exhausted.
We're at our limit.
I don't even know what to say to that...
I'm sorry.
But I guess I feel bad for you, too.
What do you mean by that?
Heave ho, heave ho.
Heave ho... Heave ho...
Lady Doux, what are you doing here?
Here you go.
One, two, one, two.
Sweepy sweep.
Your trials with Lady Doux
aren't going well, right?
Sweepy sweep.
Sweepy, sweepy sweep.
They aren't.
Yairya, I have a favor to ask.
Is there anyone who can make a
potion that'll make Lady Doux evil?
MUS – JUNIOR WITCH
Hello!
You must be Mus. I'm sure Yairya
has already filled you in, but...
Why are you so surprised?!
B-B-B-Because I told her that I couldn't
possibly do this and turned her down.
What?!
You can't even make a single
potion? You're finished!
STAB
I-I'll do it! I can do it!
Please just give me a little more time!
S-Sure... If you'll get right to it...
O-Okay!
Hm...
There's no official formulation for
a drug that draws out one's evil.
But there's someone named Mus that's
completely self-taught in her research.
There's only a slight possibility,
but she might be able to do it.
It's just she's a bit different...
Let's see... Let's see...
Is she actually going
to be able to do this?
I-It's done...
Ooh!
It's probably a bit bitter though.
GURGLE GURGLE GURGLE...
Doux can eat green peppers, so it's okay!
Bitterness aside,
is this even drinkable?
It's made only with things
good for your body...
B-But...
You need to be more cautious, Lady Doux!
There's a reaction! Sh-She
should be evil now.
How do you feel, Lady Doux?
You dummy-ass!
You chicken butt! You macaroon!
Lady Doux said something rude?!
I'll krill you!
Though she seems to be just a tad off...
But we're going in the right direction!
Can you adjust the formula?
Y-Yes!
I'm super angy!
I've never seen Lady
Doux like this before.
If we continue adjusting the formula...
It's done. Here.
It's about time, you slowypoke!
Yay!
Wah! She multiplied!
But why?!
Boom!
Let's play!
I'm hungry.
Wh-What kind of formula adjustment
could possibly lead to this?!
I-I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
She should turn back with this!
There are so many...
Douxs!
Why are you just complicating
this even more?!
I-I'll adjust it some more!
Pretty!
My eyes are flickering...
Th-This should work.
Now we're strong!
So close! Now, if she was just evil!
O-One more time!
DWAHAHAHA
FWAHAHAHA
Well, at least her voice
sounds more evil now.
I-I'm so sorry!
Well, at least Lady Doux
returned to her normal self.
I-I'm so sorry...
Let's calm down a bit.
Could I get some tea?
R-Right away!
H-Here you go.
Thanks.
Wait, is this...
It's a potion!
I'm so sorry! I mistook it for tea!
I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
Why didn't you check more carefully?!
Huh? We've switched bodies?!
Now something's been summoned!
Wow! It's a Mr. Octopus! Mr. Octopus!
Wha?!
C-Curses...
I can't do anything in this body.
H-Hey, Mus!
Do something about this!
Mus!
I'll make up for this by
cutting my stomach open!
Wait no! That's my body!
Damn it!
W-We're finally back to normal...
I knew I couldn't do it...
There's no way I could do it!
There's so much I don't know even
when I'm making one potion!
I'm so useless, and all
I do is cause trouble...
I'm just...
Doux had a lot of fun though!
Huh?
There were a lot of me, I transformed,
and then there was a Mr. Octopus!
Can all witches make lots
of potions this amazing?!
N-No! I can't even make them
the way I actually want...
Everyone above me can make potions
without making a single mistake.
All of mine are incomplete or failures.
Even today...
Then let's go ask them how
to make them together.
What?!
I-I-I couldn't possibly! Even if I go,
I'm just going to cause trouble!
Let's go!
W-W-W-Wait! Lady Doux!
I couldn't possibly!
Wait! No!
I can't believe you actually went to Mus.
Wha?! Yairya, how dare you?!
Well, I guess I have no choice.
You've brought me this incomplete
potion to make someone evil,
so you must've come to get advice, right?
U-Um, uh... yes...
I guess that's the case.
I just keep messing up and...
I'm sure it won't go well...
And I'm sure you're busy... And I'm sure
I'm bothering you... So I'll just...
If you squirm anymore,
I'm putting you into a pot.
I-I'm so sorry!
If you want to show me
something, straighten up.
Lady Doux, this way.
Yay!
H-Hey! You're using that here?!
Th-Th-Th-That might be dangerous!
It's fine. Even if something
happens, I'm here.
What just happened?
Th-This is...
I can feel my fatigue melting away.
What's going on?
I don't really know why,
but my fatigue's all gone!
Same here! My body feels so much lighter!
But why? Also, what was
all that smoke just now?
Wow!
Everyone in the castle
suddenly feels better.
That range of effect is amazing!
U-Um... This is uh...
How could you make something
like this, Mus?!
Eek!
It's brilliant!
Huh?
I've never seen a potion like this!
How in the world did you make it?
Huh?! B-But this was a failure...
It might be a failure,
but it's still amazing!
Huh?
Mus,
I want to teach you all kinds of things
and learn all kinds of things from you!
If we teach each other
things we don't know,
I'm sure we'll be able to make
something even more amazing!
Let's work together!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Thank you!
Doux, too! Doux wants to learn things!
Let's make them together, Lady Doux!
What kind of potion did
you want to make, Lady Doux?
A super yummy potion
that you can drink lots of!
So I just went through
all this for nothing...
THE HERO IS JUST TOO UNRELIABLE!
"The Hero Is Just Too Unreliable!!"
I came all this way to
take down the demon king
and somehow got separated
from my party...
Damn it.
In this situation, I should... Huh?
Boom!
Hello!
Wait! Who are you?!
Where'd you come from?!
Doux's name is Doux.
I was playing hide-and-seek with Papa
and found a hole and
slid all the way here.
What's your name, miss?
Ur. Ur the Hero.
A hero! Wow!
I may be a hero,
but there're so many of us.
I mean, there's basically a hero
for every village in existence...
Ahem. I'm looking for my party
that I've been separated from.
But first, we need to get
you back up to the surface.
Eek! A bug!
So many giant Mr. Spiders!
I can't! No one told me there'd
be bugs that huge here!
There... There has to be
some solution to this!
What's that?
Th-This is the Adventurer's Tome!
It has all kinds of knowledge and
tricks needed for adventures.
Th-There we go!
"For bug-type demons, use
sweet things or hellfire"?!
I don't have anything sweet!
And I need to be able to use powerful
magic to produce hellfire.
Doux knows how.
R-Really?
Flare!
That's not a very big flame!
They're gathering to the light!
But it's no use! There's
just too many of them!
Ah! Look!
Oh, right! Sweet things!
Okay, if we just use this...
This was a demon, too!
Of course there wouldn't be strawberries
growing in a place like this!
This is probably an earth-type.
How do I deal with this?
Strawberry!
Doux! Look up how to deal with
these earth-type demons for me!
Okay!
"How to make strawberry tarts"...
Doux!
Oh! Okay, it says to use
water for earth-type demons.
Doux has some!
Huh? Wait, you can use
water-based magic, too?!
Here you go.
It's just water!
Doux! No, these are...
They gave me a strawberry!
These were actually strawberries?!
What's the right answer here?!
"ADVENTURE, ADVENTURE!"
LYRICS: KANATA NAKAMURA
COMPOSITION AND ARRANGEMENT: YURI MORITA
SONG: DOUX
Adventure, adventure, it's
time for an adventure
Deep, deep down a pitfall
Let's look over here and look over there
Let's see everything that's down here
Go! Go! Go, go, go!
I'm down here with my friend
So it's not scary at all
Adventure, adventure, it's
time for an adventure
Deep, deep down a pitfall
Let's look over here and look over there
Let's see everything that's down here
Go! Go! Go, go, go!
I'm down here with my friend
So it's not scary at all
Looks like we were able to
at least lose the demons.
Whoa!
M-My book!
Doux, don't worry.
This demon...
There's no doubt about it.
This is the demon who sent me and
my friends flying and separated us.
Be careful!
If this thing goes berserk,
we won't be able to deal with...
Doux! W-Wait!
What are you...
She was eaten!
N-N-No! I-I need to hurry and save her!
B-But my Adventurer's Tome...
There it is!
I don't know what to do with a demon
like that unless the book tells me...
That's enough!
You're always relying on that
dumb book! This is a battlefield!
If you can't make your own decisions,
you can't protect those
you want to protect!
They're right.
I'm... I'm...
a hero!
Take that! Doux!
Whee!
Huh?
Doux, are you hurt?
I got it!
What's that?
It's a stick!
You see, this was stuck in their throat!
They were probably thrashing
around because it hurt so bad.
That's why you went into its mouth?!
B-But how did you know that
was inside their throat?
I just had a hunch.
A-A hunch?!
But... it could've swallowed you whole.
You tried to save it
without the Adventurer's Tome
or any actual solution...
But you did that, too!
Huh?
You saved me even without the book.
I've been relying on that
book this whole time...
That Adventurer's Tome was given to
me by my father, who was a great hero.
He recorded everything he learned
and experienced on his adventures.
It's filled with his desire for me
to become a full-fledged hero...
I'm so weak... that without that book...
If I don't rely on that book, I didn't
think I could protect anything.
But...
Hey, Ur!
We finally found you!
Those voices...
My party's here!
We're getting the heck outta here!
And they brought something
insane with them?!
W-W-W-Wait a m-minute! What is that?!
No idea! But it's probably
the boss of this dungeon!
Our weapons and magic
don't do anything to it!
At this rate, it's gonna catch up to us!
No! We're gonna die!
What?!
Guys! Look after her for me.
I'll buy you some time!
Wh-What are you saying, Ur?!
Yeah! And you don't even
have your Adventurer's Tome!
It's okay!
You guys and Doux have opened my eyes!
Even without that book...
I can protect others!
To think there was a hole in the forest
that connected to this dungeon.
I've been looking for you, Doux!
N-No way...
Is that...
Demon King Ahriman?!
What's he doing here?!
Papa!
"Papa"?!
Doux! I'm so sorry!
You must've been so lonely!
Nope! The hero saved me, so I was fine.
Ah! Is that so?
Wh-Wh-What's going on here, Ur?!
Why were you with the
demon king's daughter?!
U-Uh, I had no idea...
Hero's party.
If you've come this far, you
must've come to defeat me.
THE HERO'S PARTY'S PERSPECTIVE
To thank you for taking
care of Doux for me,
I'll let you have a go
at me. So come at me.
N-No thanks!
Aw, well that's no fun.
Bye-bye!